The following video is a perfect example of why I said, you have to have a hard line.
You're not coming in.
Simple as that.
You're not coming in to our sacred spaces.
You're not coming in.
This is sacred ground.
Why not?
Why can't I come in?
Because I said you're not.
This is Larry Krasner's Town Hall at Mother Bethel Church at Society Hill.
You're not coming in to our sacred spaces.
You're not coming in to our sacred space as simple as that.
Because I said you're not coming in.
I said you're not coming in.
You have no right to tell them.
You're not coming in.
Thank you.
You're not coming in our sacred space.
You'll see what it means.
I don't care.
You'll see what it means when you come up in here.
You won't see what it means.
He said don't hurt people.
Don't hurt people, he said.
Don't hurt people.
We were trying to come to the event.
You know, they denied us entry.
They have a human wall.
They have the blue wall.
So black people who were expressing compassion and who were throwing shade at other black
people who were not expressing compassion, did you realize that you were actually in
alignment with those folks?
Was it honestly that abstract of a concept that you expressing compassion in the context
of a white supremacist would be untoward?
Would in effect provoke them?
Because now they done been to HBCUs and now they got black church services.
And do you feel better now?
Do you feel still good about yourself because you had the capacity for the compassion?
Do you?
Y'all voted for this because you set a standard that it was acceptable to attack black people
for not wanting to support a white supremacist in any way in life or death.
Y'all the black ones that be telling y'all little white friends, oh, it's okay for you
to say it.
And some of y'all even had the nerve to come weeks later to say, rest in peace, Asada Shakur.
Detestable.
You're damn rude, eh?